My name is Karol Kozłowski. I was born on May 10, 2002, in Sosnowc in the city hospital at Emila Zegadłowicza Street, 3.0.1.2.0.
Mother Agnieszka, father Tomasz, I greet you.
The city of my origin is the place where everyone laughs in Poland.
Honestly, I don't know why.
It's ugly, but I saw it uglier and we don't have a market.
Currently, I live in Warsaw, in the so-called city of miracles, innovations and moments of degeneration.
And this is quite serious.
I like our capital because it shows me how our state has developed since the time of economic transformation.
No need for information is like a lesson, never too little.
I work as an engineer devops for one of the world's largest fintechs in the world, Visa Incorporated.
Remember, dear viewers, Visa is not a bank or a debit or credit card creator,
but a global system of calculating money between financial institutions,
i.e. such a very advanced machine to move numbers from place to place.
Devops sounds exotic, but in practice it is about ensuring a single-scale infrastructure
for IT projects and a wide range of automation processes.
In order not to get bored with buzzwords, I invite you to the section dedicated to my experience,
where I describe it a little more broadly.
What do I have in common with Kozłami, apart from the slang-sounding name?
Yes, I record a podcast talking to Kozłami, from young people for everyone.
You will find the link on the page or in the section dedicated to the podcast.
I am also a private investor.
In practice, it means that some of the hard-earned money I have already managed to lose both
and multiply in the cryptocurrency market.
And seriously, I think that the current monetary system and a wide range of macroeconomic conditions
are strongly pushing the middle class.
Therefore, investing is one of the few trampolines to the front.
Remember, however, that investing is involved with the risk
and it is absolutely not an investment order.
And I have honest hope that you will not listen to any of the local Warsaw network from the Internet.
Education is also something that has happened.
I have finished the information used for AGH.
Currently, I am in the course of major studies in the Warsaw Polytechnic,
although at the moment I pressed the URLOB-Dziekański,
to live a little and make some projects outside of the university.
In short, I study, but with a distance to academic drama.
My motto is to be hearty in your knowledge and praise.
What kind of book is this?
Okay, that's enough.
That's enough for health and to click on the content well.